<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>Angor Blog</title><description>A decentralized crowdfunding protocol built on Bitcoin and Nostr</description><link>https://blog.angor.io/</link><language>en</language><item><title>Angor vs. Traditional Crowdfunding</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/angor-vs-traditional-crowdfunding/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/angor-vs-traditional-crowdfunding/</guid><description>This article compares Angor to traditional crowdfunding services, outlining key differences, advantages, and potential challenges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Crowdfunding has revolutionized the way individuals and businesses raise capital, offering new investment opportunities for individuals to access private equities and diversify their portfolios. Traditional platforms like Kickstarter, Indiegogo, GoFundMe, Seedrs and Crowdcube have paved the way for countless projects, from innovative gadgets to humanitarian causes. However, as technology evolves, so do the methods of crowdfunding. Enter Angor, a decentralized crowdfunding platform leveraging Bitcoin and Nostr for enhanced security and transparency. In this article, we compare Angor to traditional crowdfunding services, highlighting the key differences, advantages, and potential challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, we compare Angor to traditional crowdfunding services, highlighting the key differences, advantages, and potential challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to Angor Testing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Platform Structure&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Centralized: Platforms like Kickstarter and Indiegogo operate as centralized entities, managing all transactions and interactions between creators and backers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Middleman Dependency: These platforms act as intermediaries, which means they have control over the fund distribution and project approval processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized: Angor operates on a decentralized model using Bitcoin for financial transactions and Nostr for communication. This removes the need for a central authority, giving more control to investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peer-to-Peer: The decentralized nature allows direct interactions between project founders and investors without relying on a middleman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Security and Fund Control&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fund Management: In traditional platforms, the platform itself holds the funds until the project meets its goal. There is a risk associated with platform security breaches or mismanagement of funds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All-or-Nothing: Many platforms follow an all-or-nothing funding model, where funds are only released if the campaign reaches its goal. If not, funds are returned to backers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-Lock Contracts: Angor uses Bitcoin’s time-lock contracts, releasing funds in stages based on project milestones. This ensures funds are only accessible when specific conditions are met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investor Control: Investors have the ability to recover unspent funds at any point, significantly reducing the risk of losing their investment due to project failure or fraud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Transparency and Accountability&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limited Updates: While traditional platforms allow project updates, these are often controlled by the platform and can be infrequent or lack detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trust Issues: Backers must trust the platform and the project creators to be transparent and honest about progress and challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nostr Integration: Angor uses Nostr, a decentralized communication protocol, for project updates. This ensures that updates are transparent and directly accessible to investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Direct Communication: Project founders can post updates directly, maintaining accountability and fostering trust through regular, detailed communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Costs and Fees&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platform Fees: Traditional platforms charge a percentage of the funds raised, typically ranging from 5% to 15%, in addition to payment processing fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hidden Costs: Additional costs may include setup fees, transfer fees, promotional fees, or charges for premium features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complex Fee Structures: The combination of various fees can make the cost structure complicated and less transparent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lower Fees: Angor charges a minimal fee of just 1%, significantly lower than traditional platforms. This is made possible by its decentralized nature, reducing operational costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simple Fee Structure: Angor offers a straightforward fee structure without hidden costs, making it easier for users to understand the total expenses involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Global Accessibility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regional Restrictions: Traditional platforms often have regional restrictions due to banking and regulatory issues, limiting global participation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currency Limitations: Transactions are usually conducted in specific currencies, which may not be convenient for international backers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Borderless Transactions: Utilizing Bitcoin allows for seamless global transactions, enabling anyone with internet access to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrency Advantage: The use of Bitcoin bypasses traditional banking systems, offers a more inclusive and accessible platform for global users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Community and Support&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Traditional Crowdfunding Platforms:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Established Communities: Traditional platforms have large, established user bases and offer community support and marketing tools to help projects gain visibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platform Support: Users benefit from customer support provided by the platform, including dispute resolution and project promotion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Angor:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing Community: As a newer platform, Angor is building its community. Early adopters have the advantage of shaping the platform’s growth and culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Support: Community support and communication are handled through decentralized channels, fostering a more peer-to-peer support system.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/angor-vs-traditional-crowdfunding.jpg</image></item><item><title>How to Test Angor: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-test-angor/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-test-angor/</guid><description>Angor is a decentralized crowdfunding project leveraging the security of Bitcoin and the transparency of Nostr.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to Angor Testing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor is a decentralized crowdfunding project leveraging the security of Bitcoin and the transparency of Nostr. Investors&apos; funds are released in stages through time-lock contracts, and unspent funds can be recovered at any point (recovered funds may incur a penalty). Testing Angor involves verifying these processes and ensuring the platform works as intended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Step-by-Step Guide to Testing Angor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1: Initial Setup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Create a Wallet on Angor&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sign up on the Angor platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate to the wallet creation section.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on &quot;Create Wallet.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angor will automatically set up the wallet for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Obtain Test Coins&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the test coins section.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on &quot;Get Test Coins.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The test coins will be added to your newly created wallet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2: Testing the Investment Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Choose a Project&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Browse the available projects on Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select a project to invest in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review the project details and milestones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Make an Investment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate to the chosen project’s page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the &quot;Invest&quot; button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter the amount you wish to invest in the provided field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &quot;Submit&quot; to confirm the transaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait for the founder to approve (this is a manual process by the founder).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait for the transaction to be confirmed on the blockchain. This may take a few minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;3. If you are testing as the founder and investor&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the project page and approve the investment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3: Creating and Managing a Project (For Founders)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Create a New Project&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate to the &quot;Create Project&quot; section on Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter the project name, description, and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define the project milestones and the corresponding time-lock contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload a banner image to make the project page more appealing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &quot;Submit&quot; to create the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Post Project Updates on Nostr&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Export the private key from Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Import the private key into a Nostr client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post updates on project progress and milestone completion on Nostr.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure updates are clear and informative for investors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Spend Funds for Milestones&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a founder, once a milestone is reached, sign the transaction to spend the funds for that milestone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the spending aligns with the milestone requirements and project goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 4: Testing Milestone Verification and Fund Release&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Monitor Project Progress&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly check the project updates on Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor the project&apos;s progress and milestone completion status as reported by the project owner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Review Milestone Status&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a milestone is due, check the milestone status update provided by the project owner on Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the reported progress aligns with the expected timeline and requirements for the milestone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;3. Release of Funds&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You Are the Founder&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As the project founder, spend the first milestone funds by signing the transaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verify that the funds are released according to the time-lock contract once a milestone is reached.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As the Investor&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait for the project founder to approve the investment and release the milestone funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Verify that subsequent milestone funds are released according to the time-lock contract as each milestone is reached.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 5: Testing Fund Recovery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Initiate Fund Recovery&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a project fails to meet its milestones, go to your project dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the recovery option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiate the fund recovery process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Receive Recovered Funds into Penalty&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confirm the recovery transaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check your funds are locked in the penalty (it will show how many days are left to recover the funds).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;3. Receive Funds out of Penalty&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait till the penalty expires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move your funds out of penalty to your wallet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 6: User Experience and Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Evaluate User Interface&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate through the Angor platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the user interface for ease of use, design, and functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure all features are accessible and intuitive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Submit Feedback&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the Angor repository on GitHub to submit your feedback as issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest improvements or provide general feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check for a response or acknowledgment from the Angor team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Discord or Telegram to discuss more and ask questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/test-angor.webp</image></item><item><title>How to Invest Using Angor</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-invest-using-angor/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-invest-using-angor/</guid><description>Angor allows you to browse various projects and invest securely using Bitcoin. Create a wallet, select a project, submit your investment for approval, and manage your funds with ease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Invest in Projects Securely with Angor: A Step-by-Step Guide&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor is a decentralized crowdfunding platform built on Bitcoin and uses Nostr for enhanced security and transparency. It allows investors to maintain control over their funds and supports direct communication between investors and founders. Here’s a step-by-step guide on how to invest using Angor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How to invest using Angor: A Step-by-step guide to follow along:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Browse for Projects&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To begin investing, you first need to find a project that interests you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visit the Angor Platform&lt;/strong&gt;: Start by going to the Angor website. If you don’t have a wallet yet, create a wallet to use Angor; otherwise, recover your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to the Projects Section&lt;/strong&gt;: Navigate to the &apos;Projects Browse&apos; tab in the main menu. This will take you to the section where all available projects are listed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/project-list.svg&quot; alt=&quot;List of project will be here&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explore the Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review Details&lt;/strong&gt;: Each project listing includes a variety of details such as the project’s objectives, the team behind it, its funding goals, and timelines. Spend some time going through these details to understand the scope and purpose of each project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assess Goals&lt;/strong&gt;: Check the funding goals to see how much the project aims to raise. This will give you an idea of the scale of the project and its financial needs. The &quot;Smart Farming Solutions&quot; project has a target amount of 50 TBTC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understand Projects Timelines&lt;/strong&gt;: Look at the project timelines to see the expected milestones and deadlines. This helps you gauge how long your investment will be tied up and when you can expect to see progress or returns. &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;For instance, the stages of the &quot;Smart Farming Solutions&quot; project include 10% completion by 30/04/2024, 30% by 20/05/2024, and 60% by 30/05/2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/project-insider.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Project Insights Overview&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking the time to thoroughly explore the projects will help you make an informed decision about where to invest your funds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Create a Wallet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you can invest in any project, you need to set up a digital wallet on Angor. If you don’t have a wallet yet, create a wallet to use Angor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to the Wallet Section&lt;/strong&gt;: Once logged in, find and click on the &apos;Wallet&apos; section from your dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create Your Wallet&lt;/strong&gt;: Follow the on-screen instructions to create your digital wallet. This typically involves:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up on the Angor platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigate to the wallet creation section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on &quot;Create Wallet.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor will automatically set up the wallet for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set a strong password to protect your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/wallet-after-creation.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Wallet after creation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back Up Recovery Phrases&lt;/strong&gt;: You’ll be given a set of recovery phrases. Store these securely, as they are essential for accessing your wallet if you forget your password.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How to Invest in a Project on Angor&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browse Available Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Explore the projects listed on Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select a Project&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose a project that interests you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review Details and Milestones&lt;/strong&gt;: Carefully read through the project’s objectives, funding goals, and expected milestones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make an Investment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to Project Page&lt;/strong&gt;: Go to the page of the project you selected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click &quot;Invest&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;: Locate and click the &quot;Invest&quot; button on the project page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter Investment Amount&lt;/strong&gt;: Input the amount of Bitcoin you wish to invest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit the Investment&lt;/strong&gt;: Confirm the transaction by clicking &quot;Submit.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/investment-page.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Investment page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wait for Approval&lt;/strong&gt;: Your investment needs to be approved by the project founder. This is a manual process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/founder-page.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Founder approval request&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/founder-pending-signature.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Founder pending signature page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transaction Confirmation&lt;/strong&gt;: Wait for the transaction to be confirmed on the blockchain, which may take a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Claim Back Funds with a Penalty&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need to withdraw your investment before the project is completed, you can do so, but note that there will be a penalty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to Your Investments&lt;/strong&gt;: From your dashboard, go to the &apos;Investments&apos; section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select the Project&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose the project from which you want to withdraw your funds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Request a Refund&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on the option to claim back your investment and follow the guided steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understand the Penalty&lt;/strong&gt;: Be aware that withdrawing your investment early will incur a penalty, deducted from the refunded amount. The specific terms of this penalty will be detailed in the project’s information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/invested-portfolio.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Portfolio Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Initiate Fund Recovery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a project fails to meet its milestones, go to your project dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the recovery option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiate the fund recovery process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Receive Recovered Funds into Penalty&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confirm the recovery transaction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check your funds are locked in the penalty (it will show how many days are left to recover the funds).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Receive Funds out of Penalty&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait till the penalty expires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move your funds out of penalty to your wallet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By following these steps, you can effectively use Angor to discover promising projects, invest your funds, and manage your investments efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy investing!&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/invest.webp</image></item><item><title>How to Raise Funds Using Angor</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-raise-funds/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/how-to-raise-funds/</guid><description>Angor is a decentralized crowdfunding platform on Bitcoin, offering secure fund management and direct investor engagement for transparent project funding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Raise Funds Securely with Angor:  Step-by-Step Guide&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor is a decentralized crowdfunding platform built on Bitcoin and uses Nostr for enhanced security and transparency. It allows founders to raise funds for their projects while maintaining control over the funds and fostering direct communication with investors. Here’s a step-by-step guide on how to raise funds using Angor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Create a Wallet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you can start raising funds, you need to set up a digital wallet on Angor. If you don’t have a wallet yet, create a wallet to use Angor. Follow the on-screen instructions to create your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigate to the wallet creation section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on &quot;Create Wallet.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor will automatically set up the wallet for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set a strong password to protect your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back Up Recovery Phrases&lt;/strong&gt;: You’ll be given a set of recovery phrases. Store these securely, as they are essential for accessing your wallet if you forget your password.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/wallet-intro.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Wallet after creation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Recovering a Wallet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you already have a wallet and need to recover it, follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Navigate to the Wallet Section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on &quot;Recover Wallet.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter Recovery Details: Paste your wallet words in the provided field.
Optionally, enter an extra word if you used one during the creation of your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set a strong password for your recovered wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confirm Backup: Ensure you have backed up your wallet words and passphrase securely.
Check the box confirming you have backed up your wallet words and passphrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complete Recovery:
Click on &quot;Create Wallet&quot; to complete the recovery process. Your wallet will be restored with the funds and transaction history intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/wallet-after-creation.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Wallet after creation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Create a Project&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once your wallet is set up, you can create a project to start raising funds. Here are the steps involved, illustrated with images of the Angor platform interface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 1: Fill in Project Metadata&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navigate to the &quot;Create Project&quot; Section&lt;/strong&gt;: Navigate to the &apos;Founder&apos; section and click on &apos;Create Project&apos;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter Project Metadata&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Name&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter a clear and descriptive name for your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About&lt;/strong&gt;: Provide detailed information about your project, including its objectives and vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Website&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter the URL of your project’s website, if available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Banner&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter the URL of your project’s banner image to make your project page visually appealing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nip 05 and Nip 57 (zaps)&lt;/strong&gt;: Fill these fields with the relevant information if applicable. Zaps are small, voluntary donations that supporters can give to your project. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoiner.guide/zap/&quot;&gt;Learn more about zaps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt;: Enter the URL of your project’s reference image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/project-metadata.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Project Metadata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &quot;Next&quot; to proceed to the next step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 2: Provide Project Info&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter Project Identifier and Founder Key&lt;/strong&gt;: These fields will be auto-generated by Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Date and Expiry Date&lt;/strong&gt;: Set the start date and the expiry date for your project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Penalty Days&lt;/strong&gt;: Define the number of penalty days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target Amount&lt;/strong&gt;: Specify the total amount of funding you aim to raise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Define Project Stages&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allocate a percentage of the total funds to each stage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set the date for each stage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &quot;Next&quot; to proceed to the next step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/project-info.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Project Info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Step 3: On-Chain Confirmation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review Project Details&lt;/strong&gt;: Review all the details of your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confirm Project Creation&lt;/strong&gt;: Once all the information is verified, click on &quot;Submit&quot; to finalize the creation of your project on the blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/on-chain.svg&quot; alt=&quot;On-Chain Confirmation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Proceeding to the Next Section&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After filling out all the required information in the Project Info section, click the &quot;Next&quot; button to move on to the On Chain section, where you will define blockchain-related parameters for your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/view-project.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Example Project View&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Post Project Updates on Nostr&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Export the private key from Angor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Import the private key into a Nostr client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post updates on project progress and milestone completion on Nostr.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure updates are clear and informative for investors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Approving Investment Requests&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once your project is live on Angor, you may start receiving investment requests from potential investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Review Requests: Navigate to the &quot;Actions&quot; section in your project dashboard to view all pending signatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/approve-signature-tab.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Approve signature tab&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approve Signatures: Approve the request through Angor. This action confirms acceptance of the investor’s contribution to your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/approving-investment.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Approving investment by founder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Spend Funds for Milestones&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a founder, once a milestone is reached, sign the transaction to spend the funds for that milestone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ensure the spending aligns with the milestone requirements and project goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/founder-stage-claim.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Founder stage funds claim&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Claiming Funds&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easily monitor project progress, release milestone funds, and handle penalties directly from your Angor dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;1. Monitor Project Progress&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regularly check the project updates on Angor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ensure that the milestones are being met as planned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/project-stats.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Project stats&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;2. Initiate Fund Release for Milestones&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once a milestone is reached, navigate to your project dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find the milestone that has been achieved and click on the &quot;Claim Funds&quot; button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sign the transaction to release the funds for that milestone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;3. Regular Fund Claim Process:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Navigate to the &quot;Funds&quot; section in your project dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the &quot;Claim Funds&quot; button for the available milestone funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sign the transaction to transfer the funds to your wallet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By following these steps, you can effectively use Angor to raise funds for your project, ensuring a smooth and transparent process from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/raise.svg</image></item><item><title>Innovative Time-Lock Contracts</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/time-lock-contracts/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/time-lock-contracts/</guid><description>Discover how Angor&apos;s innovative time-lock contracts enhance accountability and trust in crowdfunding by releasing funds at predetermined intervals based on milestone achievements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Innovative Time-Lock Contracts: Revolutionizing Crowdfunding with Angor&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-lock contracts are a cornerstone of Angor&apos;s commitment to fostering a secure and accountable environment for founders and investors. By releasing funds at predefined intervals, these contracts ensure that funded projects achieve measurable milestones before receiving additional capital. This method promotes transparency and trust throughout the funding process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How Time-Lock Contracts Enhance the Funding Experience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional funding models often disburse the entirety of an investment upfront. This can present challenges for both founders and investors. Founders may lack the impetus to prioritize resource allocation or demonstrate efficient progress. Investors, on the other hand, might face the risk of misappropriated funds or unfulfilled promises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-lock contracts address these concerns by creating a staged funding structure. Funds are released incrementally, contingent upon the completion of specific goals. This incentivizes founders to meticulously manage their resources and achieve tangible benchmarks. Investors benefit from the reassurance that their capital is directly tied to a project&apos;s development, fostering a sense of trust and shared success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Benefits of Time-Lock Contracts for Founders&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Promotes Focus and Efficiency&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knowing that subsequent funding hinges on achieving milestones compels founders to prioritize tasks and allocate resources effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Improves Transparency and Builds Trust&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-lock contracts signal a commitment to responsible use of funds, strengthening the rapport between founders and investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Reduces Risk and Enhances Credibility&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By demonstrating the ability to meet funding benchmarks, founders solidify their credibility and position themselves for future investment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Benefits of Time-Lock Contracts for Investors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Mitigates Risk of Misuse of Funds&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The staged release of capital ensures that funds are channeled towards achieving project objectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Provides Performance Visibility&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investors gain a clear view of a project&apos;s progress, enabling them to make informed decisions about continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Fosters a Collaborative Environment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shared goals outlined in the time-lock contract cultivate a sense of partnership between founders and investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Angor&apos;s Approach: A Secure and Dynamic Funding Ecosystem&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Angor&apos;s innovative time-lock contracts represent a significant step forward in creating a secure and dynamic funding ecosystem. By aligning the interests of founders and investors, these contracts empower ventures to achieve long-term success while providing investors with peace of mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Mechanics of Time-Lock Contracts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-lock contracts work by incorporating specific time-based conditions into the release of funds. Here&apos;s a closer look at how they function:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Milestone Definition&lt;/strong&gt;: At the beginning of the funding agreement, founders and investors agree on a series of milestones that must be achieved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fund Allocation&lt;/strong&gt;: Funds are locked in a smart contract and are released in stages, contingent upon the completion of the agreed milestones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress Verification&lt;/strong&gt;: Each milestone completion is verified, ensuring that the project is progressing as planned before releasing additional funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Real-World Applications and Case Studies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Enhancing Accountability in Tech Startups&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, a tech startup developing an AI-based tool received funding divided into five stages, each linked to specific development milestones. This approach kept the startup on track and provided our investors with confidence in the project&apos;s progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Promoting Sustainability in Green Energy Projects&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A green energy project utilized time-lock contracts to ensure the progressive implementation of its renewable energy solutions. By tying funding to specific milestones, the project maintained its focus and achieved significant advancements in sustainable technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Future of Time-Lock Contracts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As blockchain technology continues to evolve, the implementation of time-lock contracts will become even more sophisticated. This will enhance their ability to provide security, efficiency, and transparency in various funding scenarios. Future developments may include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced Smart Contract Features&lt;/strong&gt;: More complex conditions and triggers for fund release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integration with Other Blockchain Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;: Enhancing the security and functionality of time-lock contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wider Adoption in Various Industries&lt;/strong&gt;: Expanding the use of time-lock contracts beyond the tech and finance sectors to include industries like healthcare, education, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion: A New Era of Trust and Accountability&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, time-lock contracts are a powerful tool for enhancing accountability and trust in the startup funding process. At Angor, we are proud to lead this innovation, ensuring that our investments lead to real, measurable success. By embracing time-lock contracts, we support our founders and build a more reliable and transparent startup ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/time-lock-contracts.svg</image></item><item><title>Setting up a Bitcoin Full Node on Different Operating Systems</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/bitcoin-full-node/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/bitcoin-full-node/</guid><description>Learn how to set up a Bitcoin full node on Windows, macOS, and Linux to contribute to the Bitcoin network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Running a Bitcoin full node is a great way to support the Bitcoin network and ensure its decentralization. A full node validates transactions and blocks, helping maintain the integrity of the blockchain. Here’s a step-by-step guide to setting up a Bitcoin full node on Windows, macOS, and Linux.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hardware Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Processor (CPU):&lt;/strong&gt; A modern multicore processor is recommended. Bitcoin Core&apos;s performance benefits from a higher clock speed rather than a higher number of cores. An Intel 4 Core E3v6 3.5GHz CPU is fully sufficient for a full Bitcoin node.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Access Memory (RAM):&lt;/strong&gt; At least 8 GB of RAM is recommended, but more RAM can improve performance. The memory requirements may increase as the size of the Bitcoin blockchain grows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt; The Bitcoin blockchain is continuously growing, so you need enough storage space to accommodate it. An SSD or NVMe drive is recommended for faster synchronization and better performance compared to an HDD (Hard Disk Drive). At least 1TB of SSD/NVMe disk space is required, and 2TB is recommended as the Bitcoin blockchain is rapidly growing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Internet Connection:&lt;/strong&gt; A high-speed, stable internet connection is essential for keeping your node synchronized with the Bitcoin network. A 100Mbps connection with 5 - 10TB of bandwidth per month is sufficient.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating System:&lt;/strong&gt; Bitcoin Core, the reference implementation for a Bitcoin full node, is compatible with various operating systems, including Windows, macOS, and Linux. Choose an operating system that you are comfortable with and that is well-supported by Bitcoin Core.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Core Software:&lt;/strong&gt; Download and install the latest version of the Bitcoin Core software from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoin.org/en/download&quot;&gt;official website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Considerations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Firewall Configuration:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure that your firewall allows incoming connections to port 8333 (the default port for Bitcoin&apos;s peer-to-peer network) to enable your node to connect with other nodes on the Bitcoin network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Software Updated:&lt;/strong&gt; Regularly update your Bitcoin Core software to the latest version to benefit from security fixes and improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure your Node:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement best practices for securing your server, such as using strong passwords, keeping your operating system up-to-date, and employing any additional security measures recommended for your specific environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Setting up a Bitcoin Full Node on Windows&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download the Bitcoin Core Client:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoincore.org/en/download/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Core download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the appropriate version for Windows and download the installer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run the installer and follow the instructions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose a directory to install Bitcoin Core. The default directory is usually fine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Bitcoin Core from the Start menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first time you run Bitcoin Core, it will ask where you want to store the data. Choose a directory with at least 350 GB of free space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin Core will begin to download the blockchain. This can take several days, depending on your Internet speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure the Node:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit the &lt;code&gt;bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt; file located in the Bitcoin data directory (default: &lt;code&gt;C:\Users\YourUsername\AppData\Roaming\Bitcoin\bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add the following lines to the file to configure your node:&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;server=1
txindex=1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save and close the file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allow Connections:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open your firewall settings and allow inbound connections to port 8333.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Setting up a Bitcoin Full Node on macOS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download the Bitcoin Core Client:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoincore.org/en/download/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Core download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download the macOS version of the installer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open the downloaded .dmg file and drag Bitcoin Core to your Applications folder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open Bitcoin Core from the Applications folder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When prompted, choose a directory with at least 350 GB of free space for storing the blockchain data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin Core will start downloading the blockchain, which may take a while.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure the Node:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit the &lt;code&gt;bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt; file located in the Bitcoin data directory (default: &lt;code&gt;~/Library/Application Support/Bitcoin/bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add the following lines:&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;server=1
txindex=1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save and close the file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allow Connections:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to System Preferences &amp;gt; Security &amp;amp; Privacy &amp;gt; Firewall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow inbound connections to Bitcoin Core.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Setting up a Bitcoin Full Node on Linux&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download the Bitcoin Core Client:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoincore.org/en/download/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Core download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download the Linux version suitable for your distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open a terminal and navigate to the directory where you downloaded the file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extract the tarball and install Bitcoin Core:&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;tar -xzf bitcoin-*.tar.gz
sudo install -m 0755 -o root -g root -t /usr/local/bin bitcoin-*/bin/*
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run Bitcoin Core:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start Bitcoin Core by running &lt;code&gt;bitcoind&lt;/code&gt; in the terminal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose a directory with at least 350 GB of free space for storing the blockchain data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin Core will begin downloading the blockchain. This can take several days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure the Node:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit the &lt;code&gt;bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt; file located in the Bitcoin data directory (default: &lt;code&gt;~/.bitcoin/bitcoin.conf&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add the following lines:&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;server=1
txindex=1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save and close the file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allow Connections:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure your firewall to allow inbound connections on port 8333.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Running a Bitcoin full node is a rewarding way to support the Bitcoin network. It requires some initial setup and ongoing maintenance, but it ensures you have a fully validating node that helps maintain the integrity of the network. Ensure your system remains secure and up-to-date, and enjoy being a part of the decentralized Bitcoin community.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/bitcoin-full-node.svg</image></item><item><title>What is an Initial Coin Offering (ICO)?</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/ico/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/ico/</guid><description>Dive deep into the world of Initial Coin Offerings (ICO), exploring how this innovative crowdfunding mechanism leverages cryptocurrency to fund new projects and the nuances that differentiate it from traditional IPOs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;An Initial Coin Offering (ICO) is a funding mechanism in the digital currency market inspired by the traditional Initial Public Offering (IPO) in the stock market. Just as capital is raised in the stock market, the crypto world utilizes ICOs to gather funds for new projects. If you&apos;re curious about what ICOs entail, this article will guide you through every aspect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What is an ICO?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Initial Coin Offering (ICO), similar to an Initial Public Offering (IPO) in the stock market, is a form of crowdfunding using cryptocurrency. It is essentially a presale, where a blockchain project offers coins, tokens, or digital currency to investors as a way to raise capital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How Does an ICO Work?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An ICO operates similarly to an IPO but is designed specifically for blockchain projects. Here’s what typically happens in an ICO:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whitepaper Release:&lt;/strong&gt; The organizer provides a detailed whitepaper, which includes technical details, the project&apos;s objectives, the duration of the ICO, and its tokenomics, to potential investors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conducting the ICO:&lt;/strong&gt; Once the whitepaper is published, a campaign period is set during which investors can commit a specific amount of digital or fiat currency but do not receive any tokens yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Distribution:&lt;/strong&gt; If the funds raised are below the project&apos;s target, the project must refund the investors. If the ICO is successful, tokens are distributed to investors’ wallets at a predetermined date according to the terms of the ICO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ICO vs. IPO: Key Differences&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulation:&lt;/strong&gt; ICOs typically face less stringent regulations compared to the extensive regulations governing IPOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; ICOs rely on a whitepaper, while IPOs involve a thorough examination of financial statements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investors:&lt;/strong&gt; ICOs are accessible to the general public, whereas IPOs often cater to institutional investors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; ICOs can conclude as soon as the smart contract and whitepaper are complete, unlike IPOs which can take months to organize.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital Use:&lt;/strong&gt; Both are used for raising capital, but the methods and accessibility differ significantly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Advantages of ICOs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralization:&lt;/strong&gt; Most ICOs are decentralized, preventing any manipulation of results and enhancing security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marketing:&lt;/strong&gt; ICOs are usually community-driven, which facilitates easier and more effective marketing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Liquidity:&lt;/strong&gt; Tokens can easily be traded on various exchanges, providing high liquidity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potentially High Returns:&lt;/strong&gt; Correctly chosen ICOs can yield substantial returns, as demonstrated by the early investors in Ethereum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Disadvantages of ICOs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Risks:&lt;/strong&gt; The biggest downside is the potential for fraud; many ICOs are scams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulatory Uncertainty:&lt;/strong&gt; The legal framework surrounding ICOs is still evolving, which can pose risks to participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Alternatives to ICOs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial Exchange Offerings (IEOs):&lt;/strong&gt; Similar to ICOs but conducted on cryptocurrency exchange platforms, offering greater security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Token Offerings (STOs):&lt;/strong&gt; These are similar to ICOs but involve tokens that are legally recognized as securities, requiring adherence to stricter regulatory standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Peak Era of ICOs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During 2017-2018, ICOs were highly popular, attracting significant attention and investment. However, this period also saw a rise in fraudulent schemes, leading to increased scrutiny and legal issues for some promoters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How to Participate in an ICO?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nowadays, ICOs have evolved into IEOs. To participate, one typically needs an account with a cryptocurrency exchange where the IEO is being hosted. This ensures a level of pre-verification of the project by the exchange, reducing the risk of fraud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FAQs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is participating in an ICO legal?&lt;/strong&gt;
There are no universal legal prohibitions on participating in ICOs, but local regulations may vary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I find ICOs?&lt;/strong&gt;
Most exchanges that host ICOs have dedicated pages listing upcoming offerings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do I launch an ICO?&lt;/strong&gt;
To launch an ICO, you need a smart contract, a comprehensive whitepaper, and a community to market the ICO.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/ico.svg</image></item><item><title>Bitcoin, A Digital Revolution</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/bitcoin/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/bitcoin/</guid><description>Explore the transformative journey of Bitcoin from its inception to its current status as a pivotal player in the financial world.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, often hailed as the first decentralized digital currency, has undeniably transformed the landscape of financial transactions worldwide. Its inception in 2009 by an anonymous entity known as Satoshi Nakamoto marked the beginning of what would soon become a global phenomenon in both technology and investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;A Revolutionary Inception&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of Bitcoin was introduced to the world through a whitepaper titled &quot;Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System.&quot; This document proposed a system where transactions could be processed directly between parties without the need for an intermediary, such as a bank. This was made possible by blockchain technology, a decentralized ledger that records all transactions across a network of computers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The Rise of Digital Gold&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin&apos;s transformation from a simple idea to a significant asset is remarkable. Initially priced at just a few cents, its value skyrocketed to an all-time high of $73,738 in March 2024. This dramatic increase was driven by its widespread acceptance among investors and the general public, who view it as a dependable store of value, commonly referred to as &apos;digital gold&apos;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Challenges and Volatility&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite its success, Bitcoin has faced its share of challenges. Its volatility is well-documented, with prices fluctuating wildly based on regulatory news, technological developments, and market sentiment. Furthermore, concerns about its use in illegal activities, energy consumption of mining operations, and regulatory scrutiny continue to pose challenges to its wider adoption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Bitcoin&apos;s Impact on the Financial Ecosystem&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The influence of Bitcoin extends beyond individual investments. It has prompted the development of thousands of other cryptocurrencies, each presenting unique innovations. It has also pressured traditional financial institutions to explore and adopt blockchain technologies to stay relevant in this rapidly evolving digital age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Looking Forward&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we look to the future, Bitcoin remains at the forefront of the cryptocurrency movement. With increasing institutional investment and technological advancements, such as the integration of the Lightning Network for faster transactions, Bitcoin&apos;s role in shaping the financial landscape continues to be significant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a seasoned investor or a curious observer, the journey of Bitcoin is a compelling testament to the power of innovation and the ongoing quest for decentralized and transparent financial systems. It&apos;s clear that Bitcoin, and the cryptocurrency movement it sparked, are here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/bitcoin.svg</image></item><item><title>Decentralized Social Networking</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/nostr/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/nostr/</guid><description>Explore Nostr, a revolutionary decentralized protocol promising a censorship-resistant and truly global social network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Nostr: The Future of Decentralized Social Networking&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an age where our digital freedoms are increasingly threatened by censorship and centralized control, the quest for a truly open and decentralized social network has never been more crucial. Enter Nostr, a simple protocol that is gaining attention for its potential to foster a resilient and censorship-resistant global social network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Nostr?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nostr stands for &quot;Notes and Other Stuff Transmitted by Relays.&quot; It is a protocol rather than an app, which means it provides a foundational standard that anyone can use to build their own applications. Nostr utilizes a straightforward JSON-based event model, coupled with elliptic-curve cryptography for secure communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Features of Nostr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplicity:&lt;/strong&gt; The protocol revolves around simple event objects, making it easy for developers to create clients and relays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resilience:&lt;/strong&gt; Nostr does not depend on any central server. Instead, it operates through a network of relays, enhancing its resistance to censorship and server failures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verifiability:&lt;/strong&gt; Thanks to public-key cryptography, it&apos;s straightforward to verify that messages genuinely originate from their claimed senders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Do We Need Nostr?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional social media platforms manipulate user attention for advertising, employ addictive mechanics, and control content through opaque algorithms. Moreover, these platforms have the ultimate authority over user participation and speech. Nostr addresses these issues by removing central points of control, thus democratizing social interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Involved with Nostr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Using Nostr:&lt;/strong&gt; You can join the Nostr network by choosing a client app suitable for your device, whether it&apos;s web, iOS, Android, or desktop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn and Explore:&lt;/strong&gt; Understand more about how Nostr works and what makes it unique by delving into the technical details of the protocol.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute:&lt;/strong&gt; The Nostr community thrives on contributions from developers and enthusiasts. Whether it&apos;s by coding, hosting a relay, or participating in community discussions, there&apos;s a role for everyone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Nostr, an Introduction&quot; by scsibug&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Why I’m Betting Big on Nostr&quot; by Max Webster&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Why Nostr Matters&quot; by Jameson Lopp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Micro Tools for Nostr Users&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;notes.blockcore.net:&lt;/strong&gt; A Nostr client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nostr.band:&lt;/strong&gt; A tool that indexes Nostr and makes it searchable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nostr.watch:&lt;/strong&gt; Tracks and displays stats of all public relays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nostr Profile Manager:&lt;/strong&gt; Helps manage profile metadata and relay lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Movement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Nostr continues to grow, more users and developers are joining the movement toward a decentralized, user-driven social network. By choosing to explore and contribute to Nostr, you&apos;re not just adopting a new platform; you&apos;re advocating for a future where social media is open, transparent, and inclusive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out Nostr today and become part of a community that values freedom and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;468&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5W-jtbbh3eA?si=N1WTorLKL0uwLsU_&quot; title=&quot;Decentralized Social Networking&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; allowfullscreen&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/nostr.svg</image></item><item><title>Welcome to the Angor Blog!</title><link>https://blog.angor.io/posts/angor/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.angor.io/posts/angor/</guid><description>Discover the new Angor Blog, your ultimate resource for Bitcoin investment insights and updates on the Angor platform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the inaugural post of the &lt;strong&gt;Angor Blog&lt;/strong&gt;—your new go-to resource for everything related to Bitcoin investments and our platform. We&apos;re thrilled to launch this blog as a part of our commitment to not only providing exceptional investment opportunities but also educating and updating our community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why Follow the Angor Blog?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our blog will feature a rich mix of educational content, latest news, and in-depth articles that cater to both seasoned investors and newcomers in the cryptocurrency world. Here’s what you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educational Articles&lt;/strong&gt;: Learn about Bitcoin, investing strategies, and how to maximize your use of the Angor platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Updates&lt;/strong&gt;: Stay informed about the latest enhancements and features of Angor, ensuring you make the most out of every investment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investment Tips&lt;/strong&gt;: Get advice from top experts in the field, helping you to make informed decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded><image>https://blog.angor.io/images/angor.svg</image></item></channel></rss>